[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What celebrated film director worked on the 1977 romantic comedy movie Annie Hall?", "correct_answer": "Woody Allen", "incorrect_answers": ["Tim Burton", "Martin Scorsese", "Oliver Stone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the note the kids leave with the babysitters body in the movie Dont Tell Mom the Babysitters Dead:\n____________________ inside. Died of natural causes.", "correct_answer": "Nice old lady", "incorrect_answers": ["We dont know who is", "The babysitter is", "Our mother is"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film The Big Lebowski, The Dude refers to a certain animal as a marmot.  What is the correct name for this creature featured in the movie?", "correct_answer": "ferret", "incorrect_answers": ["hedgehog", "badger", "mink"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of insect is often referred to as a white ant, although it is not related to the ant species?", "correct_answer": "Termite", "incorrect_answers": ["A type of small spider", "Head louse", "A type of albino wasp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Lord of the Rings, what was the name of the bread given by the Elves to the Fellowship?", "correct_answer": "Lembas", "incorrect_answers": ["Sindarin", "Athelas", "Quenya"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not one of the state-changing processes through which water goes in nature?", "correct_answer": "Concentration", "incorrect_answers": ["Condensation", "Precipitation", "Sublimation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the Marx Brothers appeared in the 1933 comedy movie Duck Soup?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Groucho", "Chico", "Zeppo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song by Madonna does Princess Fiona sing at the end of the first Shrek movie?", "correct_answer": "Like a Virgin", "incorrect_answers": ["Express Yourself", "You Must Love Me", "Take a Bow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character from the movie Steel Magnolias delivered this memorable line?\nAll gay men have track lightin. And all gay men are named Mark, Rick, or Steve.", "correct_answer": "Clariee", "incorrect_answers": ["Truvy", "MLynn", "Annelle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Crow, who says the line Childhoods over the moment you know youre gonna die.?", "correct_answer": "Top Dollar", "incorrect_answers": ["Officer Albrecht", "T-Bird", "Grange"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What part of a duck or goose is used for the preparation of the French meal Foie gras?", "correct_answer": "Liver", "incorrect_answers": ["Breast", "Skin", "Wings"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pico da Bandeira, Pico do Cruzeiro and Pedra da Mina are three of the numerous mountains located in this South American country.", "correct_answer": "Brazil", "incorrect_answers": ["Argentina", "Chili", "Peru"]}]